

RUBEN MAVAREZ

WEB DEVELOPER JR

PROFILE

NAME: Ruben Mavarez Boscan

BIRTH: 18 de Abril, 1995

ADDRESS: Hidalgo 1637, CABA, Argentina

PHONE: +54 11 3825-9649

MAIL: rubenmavarezb@gmail.com

I'm a 25 years old frontend developer with knowledge on technology such as HTML, CSS, JS, Python and actually learning Backend Development. Able to work under pressure and always up for a new challenge and open to learn new languages and technologies. Anything that helps me grow personally and professionally is welcome.

INTERESTS

Web Design

Frontend development

Web Testing

Bug Fixing

UX/UI

CMS

SKILLS

HTML	••••
CSS/SASS	••••
CSS Frameworks	••••
Javascript	• • • • •
jQuery	• • • • •
React	• • • • •
Python	••••
Django	••••
CMS	• • • • •

EXPERIENCE

2020-PRESENT GLAMIT

Frontend Developer Jr:

Developing the frontend of web designs in HTML, CSS,

JS

Maintaining webpages of clients

Design with CMS Vtex

2020-PRESENT CODERHOUSE

Mentor in Javascript and React:

Helping students in classes

Give support and feedback to student's code

Revise the challenges of each class

2020-2020 GLOBANT

Web UI Jr, Project Smile Direct Club:

Creating components based on HTML, CSS, Bulma and IS

Learning Vue.JS and Contentful to migrate old components to a new environment.

Maintaining the frontend of the client's Django CMS

EDUCATION

2020-2021 CODERHOUSE

Backend development with MERN and Typescript Frontend with Javascript

2020-2020 UDEMY

Frontend with React (Hooks, Context, Redux, MERN) Advanced Javascript

2020-2020 EDUCACION IT

Web development with Django Python Programming

2019-2020 ESCUELA DA VINCI

Web & Mobile Design

CLICK ON THE ICONS AND GO TO MY SOCIAL MEDIA:



